（英国 伦敦）
他们说 如果你想看到未来
They say if you wantto glimpse the future,
只需看眼过去即可
just look behind you.
我以前觉得那是瞎扯淡
I used to think that was bollocks.
但现在我知道了
But now I realize.
你没法逃离过去
you can't outrun the past.
我们还是孩子的时候
When we were kids,
你会去和最壮的家伙打架
you'd start fights with the toughest bastards in the yard.
但每次都是我介入帮你打赢的
But I was the one who had to step in and finish them.
你去拐角的超市里偷东西
You'd steal from the corner shop,
但最后
but it was me.
挨打的却是我
who'd brave the old man's belt.
我希望你能长大
I'd hoped you'd outgrown it.
我希望在黑帮里的生活
That playing the gangster.
能让你更坚强 更聪明 更强大
made you harder, smarter, better.
但是内心深处 我知道你肯定是这个下场
But deep down, I guess I always knew you'd end up like this,
我教你的那些毫无用处
despite everything I did teach you.
但是
Still,
你还是我的亲人
you're my flesh and blood.
所以我还是要对你负责
So you remain my cross to bear.
好好休息吧 弟弟
Rest now, little brother,
让我把你最后的活干完
while I settle your one last score.
你们照顾好我弟弟
You take care of my brother.
要是他出了什么事
Anything happens to him,
我会来找你们算账
I'll come by looking for you.
来 拿着
Here. Hold this.
手榴弹！
Grenade!
《速度与激情7》
说吧 唐 你要把我带到哪里去？
Come on, Dom. So where are you taking me?
都说大路有助于人们思考
They say an open road helps you think.
思考你从哪里来 要到哪里去
about where you've been, where you're going.
所以你还是什么都不记得？
So you don't remember any of this yet?
这不公平
That's not fair.
你知道我不记得了
You know I don't.
那你到底想给我看什么？
So what is it exactly that you're trying to show me?
那个
That.
车赛
Race Wars.
我们以前经常来这里吗？
We used to come here?
「来这里」？
"Come here"?
我们是创始人
We invented it.
保持发动机转速在每秒9000转以下
Keep it under 9, 000 RPMs.
那小子的活塞马上就会爆掉的
Kid's gonna fry his pistons after the first 200.
你知道这不是我的风格 要么赛车要么死 对吧？
You know that's not my style. I gotta ride or die, right?
你就把这场比赛开好吧？
How about you just ride on this one?
准备好了吗？
Are you ready?
我看你是准备好了！
I know you're ready!
开始！
Go!
嘿 干得不错
Hey, nice job.
嘿！
Hey!
我常常听说你的事
That's the girl I heard so much about.
你之前跑哪里去了 神秘美女？
Where you been at, ghost girl?
神秘美女
Ghost girl.
莱蒂 这他妈怎么回事？
Letty, what the hell?
卧槽 厉害！这姑娘的勾拳还是那么厉害啊 老大
Damn, dawg! Girl's still got that swing, homie.
你一直不禁打
You never could take a punch.
是啊 是啊
Right, right.
嘿 你回来了我真高兴
Hey, man. I'm glad you're back, man.
见到你太棒了！
It's good to see you!
我也很高兴 赫克托
Good to see you, Hector.
好吧 我们到了 杰克
All right. We made it, Jack.
- 耶 我们到了！- 是啊 我们到了
- Yeah, we made it! - Yeah, we made it.
现在让我找找那个开门的按钮在哪
Now I just gotta find that door button.
小家伙 你知道开门的按钮在哪吗？你知道吗？
Buddy, where's the door button at? Do you know?
- 嗨 - 嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
对啊 我还不熟悉这车
Yeah, of course. I'm new to this.
是啊 你看上去就不像是开房车的人
Yeah, you don't seem like the minivan type.
的确不怎么像
No, not exactly.
嘿 小家伙 和我击个掌吧？
Hey, buddy, you gonna give me a high five?
等等 等等 等等！等等 击掌！
Wait, wait, wait! Wait, high five!
好的 就是这样 小家伙
All right. Yeah, buddy.
谢谢 谢谢
Appreciate it. Thank you.
别担心 你马上就能习惯了
Don't worry. You'll get used to this in no time.
是啊 我就怕这个呢
Yeah, that's what I'm afraid of.
我第一次看到这个的时候
First time I saw this,
还觉得这有点可笑
I thought it was kind of funny.
我想现在可笑的是我
I guess now the joke's on me.
你要干什么？
What are you doing?
我早就该这么做了
What I should've done a long time ago.
别这样！
Stop it!
你看看
Look at it.
这就是真相
It's the truth.
那天我失忆了
That's the date that I lost my memory.
那天莱蒂就死了
That's the date that Letty died.
- 我出生了 - 不
- and I was born. - No.
你从来没死
You never died.
你知道当你看着我 能回想15年的回忆
Do you know how hard it is for me when you look at me.
对我来说有多难受吗？
and you see me through 15 years of memories?
我们有过那些美好的回忆
Every beautiful moment we've ever had.
我能在你的眼里看到
I see it in your eyes.
我给不了你什么
I can't give that to you.
我什么都没有
I got nothing.
你有我
You got me.
但你只有我的一部分
And you've got only a piece of me.
我得去找我自己
I have to find myself.
为了自己
For me.
再见 唐
Goodbye, Dom.
（外交安全局 洛杉矶分部）
你很失望 是吧？
You're disappointed, aren't you?
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
上一次逮捕
The last arrest.
太容易了 目标都没逃跑
He was too easy. Target didn't even run.
啊 没事
Ah, it's okay.
我正好有机会练练手
Gives me a chance to hit the iron.
而且还能让我锻炼敲章的能力
Also lets me work on my stamping skills.
你真不擅长撒谎
You're a terrible liar.
明天见 老板
See you tomorrow, boss.
- 明天见 - 别待太久了
- I'll see you then. - Don't stay too late.
我想待多久待多久
I'll stay as long as I want, woman.
我就知道你会这么说
I knew you would say that.
伊莲娜？
Elena?
这是什么？
What's this?
这是你要的推荐信
It's the letter of recommendation you asked for.
我写的都是我真心所想
Just know I meant every word in there.
谢谢 霍布斯
Thanks, Hobbs.
谢谢你做的一切
Thanks for everything.
拜托 这气氛太伤感了
Come on, way too sentimental right now.
回家吧 晚安
Get home. Good night.
好吧 晚安
Okay. Good night.
稍等
Just one sec.
你肯定不是IT部门的
You sure as hell ain't the IT guy.
所以你最好告诉我你是谁 要不然我就用六种不同的方法折断那根手指
So you better start talking before I break that finger six different ways.
然后插在见不到太阳的地方
and stick it right where the sun doesn't shine.
你是霍布斯探员 对吧？
Agent Hobbs, right?
没错
That's right.
在这个世界上
I'm also the last man on Earth.
你最不该黑的电脑就是我的
whose computer you want to be hacking into.
孩子 你惹上大麻烦了
You just earned yourself a dance with the devil, boy.
你被逮捕了
You're under arrest.
我对你的电脑不关心
I don't care about your computer.
我来是想找那个让我弟弟瘸腿的小队
I'm here for the team that crippled my brother.
没有什么狗屁小队
There ain't no goddamn team.
这里只有一个人 他就站在你面前
It was just one man, and he's standing right in front of you.
那个姑娘说得对
The lady was right.
你真不擅长撒谎
You are a terrible liar.
操他妈的IT男
Goddamn IT guys.
霍布斯！
Hobbs!
掩护我！
On me!
伊莲娜！
Elena!
霍布斯？
Hobbs?
霍布斯！
Hobbs!
好了 小家伙 我们得走了 我们要迟到了
All right, buddy. We gotta go. We're gonna be late.
来吧
Come on.
好吧 你觉得怎么样？
Okay, what do you think?
一个漂移去学校吗？
Parking brake slide right up to the school?
妈妈呢？
Where's Mommy?
我不知道 她在楼上 她马上就来
I don't know. She's up there. She's coming.
哦
Oh.
我们走吧
Here we go.
小心你的头
Watch your head.
唐 你有个包裹！
Dom, you have a package out here!
是东京寄来的
It's from Tokyo.
东京？
Tokyo?
怎么？韩想要把我变成一个涡轮增压机？
What? Is Han trying to convert me over to a turbocharger?
好吧 你准备好了吗？
All right, you ready?
我们走
There we go.
- 耶！- 嘿 小家伙 汽车可不会飞哦
- Yeah! - Hey, buddy. Cars don't fly.
嘿 车子不会飞
Hey, cars don't fly.
这个就会飞对吧？
This one did, huh?
布莱恩开房车 真是今非昔比了
Brian in a minivan. Things have changed.
他很不习惯 唐
He's struggling, Dom.
他不想让我知道
He doesn't want me to see it,
但是那个白色的围栏就像是他身上的锚 我看得出来
but the white picket fence is like an anchor on him. I can tell.
我前几天晚上想和他谈谈这事 你知道他说了什么吗？
I tried to talk to him the other night. You know what he said?
他不想念那些女孩 他也不想那些车
He doesn't miss the girls, he doesn't miss the cars.
他想念的是子弹
He misses the bullets.
让他习惯这一切 给他点时间
Let him settle in. Give him time.
九个月怎么样？
How does nine months sound?
我又怀孕了
I'm having another baby.
你还没有告诉他 对吧？
And you didn't tell him, did you?
你一定要告诉他
You gotta tell him.
我不想让他对自己的生活失望
I don't want him to be disappointed with his life.
对我失望
With me.
他永远不会对你失望的
He will never be disappointed with you.
你是他遇到过的最好的事
You're the best thing that's ever happened to him.
谢谢
Thank you.
喂
Yeah?
多米尼克·托莱多
Dominic Toretto.
你还不认识我
You don't know me.
不过快了
You're about to.
趴下！
Get down!
杰克！
Jack!
他的锁骨碎裂了
Shattered his collarbone,
腿也骨折了两处
fractured his leg in two places.
他今天早上才从昏迷状态醒转
He only regained consciousness this morning.
他开口第一句话就是「把唐给我找来」
The first thing he said was, "Get me Dom."
他在里面
He's in there.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
我没事
I'm fine.
他在等我们 走吧
He's waiting. Let's go.
人给你带来了
Got something for you.
你要的文件
Your files.
谢谢
Thank you.
你冒着生命危险保护这个自由世界 他们给你啥了？
You risk life and limb to save the free world and what do they give you?
果冻 还有一部糟糕的七十年代电视剧
Jell-O and a bad '70s TV show.
其实还是有一些好处的
You know, it's got its perks.
- 海绵浴就很舒服 - 爸！
- Sponge baths ain't that bad. - Dad!
对不起 宝贝
I'm sorry, baby.
「爸」？
"Dad"?
宝贝 我想让你见个人 他是…
Honey, I want to introduce you to somebody. He's a…
他是个老朋友
He's an old friend.
去和他问好吧
Go on and say hello.
你是多米尼克·托莱多 对吧？
Dominic Toretto, right?
我爸说 有次他把你教训了一顿
My dad said he kicked your ass once.
小姑娘 说话注意点
Young lady, watch your mouth.
你爸吃了太多止痛药了
Your dad's on heavy pain meds.
他的回忆可能已经不是很清晰了
I can understand if his history is a little hazy.
- 我觉得不会 - 好了宝贝 够了
- I doubt it. - All right, honey, that's enough.
你跟伊莲娜去买点吃的
I want you to go get something to eat with Elena.
我要跟托莱多谈谈 懂了吗？
while me and Toretto have a talk. You hear me?
走吧 小美女 我们去吃曲奇
Come on, lady. Let's get some cookies.
别吃太多
Watch that mouth.
谁干的？
Who did this?
你还记得欧文·肖吗？
You remember Owen Shaw?
那个我们翻了大半个伦敦抓到的那个
The one we tore half of London down trying to get.
这回是他的大哥
Well, this is his big bad brother.
看看这份文件
Take a look at this.
德卡特·肖
Deckard Shaw.
英国特种部队的杀手
British Special Forces assassin.
那种任何政府
The kind of unique asset.
都不会承认的影子部队
that no government would ever admit to employing.
绝密行动部队
Black Ops boys.
更糟的是 他们培养出了个麻烦
Worse. They created a monster.
起初觉得肖的那股狠劲是必须的
They felt Shaw was a necessary evil.
直到最后
until eventually.
他们发现他可有可无
they decided he was unnecessary.
他的那种能力
The powers that be.
已经超过了限度
felt that he knew just a little bit too much.
帮忙的后来帮了倒忙
The asset became a liability.
上面派了20个顶尖高手想除掉他
So they sent in 20 elite operatives to retire him.
但他们失手了
And they missed.
这是六年前的事情
That was six years ago,
肖之后一直毫无踪迹
and Shaw's been a ghost ever since.
直到现在
Until now.
我怎么才能找到他？
How do I find him?
官方的回复 别去找他
The official answer is, you don't.
他杀了韩
He killed Han.
还差点杀光我一家人
Almost killed my family.
他还差点把我整进尸体袋里呢
He also tried to put me in a body bag, too.
等我出院了 我要狠狠打到他
Which is why when I get out, I'm gonna put a hurt on him so bad.
后悔老妈把自己生出来
he's gonna wish his mama had kept her legs closed.
但这之前 官方对你的要求是
But until then, my official answer to you.
静待其变
is stand down.
你知道我做不到的
Now, you know I can't do that.
我懂你 唐
I do know you, Dom.
所以我要跟你说
Which is why now I give you.
兄弟间的真心话
the brother-to-brother answer.
你该怎么做就这么做
You do whatever it is you gotta do.
等你找到那混蛋
When you find that sumbitch,
帮我个忙
just do me one favor.
什么忙？
What's that?
千万别失手
Don't miss.
（多米尼亚共和国 蒙特克里斯蒂）
非常谢谢你让我住在这里 芒多
Thank you so much for letting us stay, Mando.
但愿这不会太麻烦你
I hope it's not a problem.
听我说 唐要想两天内安全偷渡进里约
Listen, Dom needed a safe delivered to Rio in two days.
那才是麻烦
That was a problem.
在多米尼亚照顾他的家人 简直跟度假一样
Hosting his family in the Dominican Republic, that is vacation.
有人要是敢在这里惹你
Anyone messes with you here,
那就惹了整个国家
they mess with the entire country.
你是安全的
You'll be safe.
是的 是的 他们到了 我亲自去机场接他们的
Yeah, yeah, they're here. I picked them up myself at the airport.
等下 你哥哥
Hold on. Your brother.
唐
Dom.
喂 米娅 是我
Yeah, Mia, it's me.
那边情况怎么样？
How's it going there?
我们在芒多家
We're at Mando's.
这地方跟个堡垒一样
This place is like a fortress.
你得看看布莱恩 他完全进入了联邦调查局模式
You should see Brian. He's in full FBI mode.
芒多的车库都被他改造成个监控站了
He built a surveillance hub in Mando's garage and everything.
你那边呢？找到是谁要对付我们了吗？
What about you? Did you find out who's after us?
看起来我们在伦敦造的孽找上门了
Looks like the sins of London have followed us home.
布莱恩什么反应？
How did Buster take the news?
我还没告诉他
I can't tell him.
如果他知道我又怀了 他肯定会留在我们身边
If he knew about the baby, he'd stay here with us.
现在这种情况 你需要他在你身边
And with all that's going on, you're gonna need him by your side.
好好照顾他 保证他的安全就行
Just watch out for him. Keep him safe.
最后 一定要一起回来
And come home together.
告诉布莱恩 我两天后在洛杉矶跟他碰头
Tell Brian I'll see him in LA in two days.
你去哪里？
Where are you going?
东京
Tokyo.
我得接韩回家
I'm bringing Han home.
当局仍在调查
Authorities are still trying to determine.
不到36小时前 于洛杉矶市中心发生的
the motive behind this daring attack here at the office.
针对美国外交安全局办公室的袭击
of the US Diplomatic Security Service in downtown Los Angeles.
背后的真正目的
less than 36 hours ago.
消息还在不断更新
Facts are still coming in,
但目前我们知道的是
but what is known is the suspect entered.
嫌犯当时处于大楼第四层…
the building's fourth floor…
嘿
Hey.
- 你还好吧？- 没事
- You okay? - Yeah.
这家伙真是步步相逼
This guy's just relentless.
所以唐才需要你
That's why Dom needs you.
你俩需要在他再次对我们的家人
You two need to find this guy and you need to stop him.
下手前 找到并阻止他
before he does any more damage to our family.
知道吗 我…
You know, I just…
我已经搞砸太多事情了
I've screwed up so many things.
这次要再搞砸 我都受不了自己了
I couldn't live with myself if I screw this up, too.
你不会的
You won't.
我相信你
I believe in you.
我相信我们 这才是最重要的
I believe in us. That's all that matters.
我爱你 布莱恩
I love you, Brian.
我爱你 宝贝
I love you, baby.
但你要保证 这次之后 我们就金盆洗手
Just promise me, after this, we're done.
不再接任务 不再有敌人
No more jobs, no more enemies.
回到我们身边来
Come back to us.
我不会让你失望的 米娅
I won't let you down, Mia.
我知道
I know.
（日本 东京）
嗨 肖恩！
Hey, yo, Sean!
嗨 看看这个 伙计
Hey, check this out, man.
那边有个家伙想跟新晋甩尾王赛一把
This dude over here want to race the new DK.
今晚算了 小闪
Not tonight, Twinkie.
他说认识韩
Said he knew Han.
韩说过你很快 但没说这么快
Han said you was fast, but not that damn fast.
谁说美国肌肉男不会漂移了？
Who said American muscle can't drift?
韩总是说 他的敌人都被甩在他身后
Han mentioned he left his enemies in his rearview.
这事他从来不多说
He never talked about it much.
他总不把心思说明白
Always playing it close to the vest.
我们在现场找回了些东西
We found a couple things by the crash.
但也没留下多少东西
Wasn't much left.
吉赛尔
Gisele.
对了
Oh, yeah.
还有一样东西
There's one more thing.
我还找到这个
I found this.
肯定对他有什么特别的意义
Must have meant something to him.
等你找到杀韩的凶手
When you find the guy that killed Han,
你打算怎么做？
what are you going to do?
语言已不足以形容
Words ain't even been invented yet.
都说要纪念那些离我们远去的人 最好的办法
They say to live in the hearts of those we leave behind.
就是好好活下去
is not to die.
但他让你落得如此下场
But he put you in this grave.
那我也要他血债血偿
So now I'll do the same to him.
我不想再参加葬礼了
I can't do no more funerals.
先是韩
First Han.
现在霍布斯也进医院了
Now Hobbs is laid up, of all people.
我们都成了猎物
We're being hunted.
要知道那家伙肯定在某个角落看着我们 对吧？
You know he's out there somewhere watching, right?
但愿如此
I hope so.
这就代表他不会走远
Means he's close.
布莱恩 你要发誓
Just promise me, Brian,
别再有葬礼了
no more funerals.
那就最后一个
Just one more.
他的
His.
你不应该招惹我的家人
You never should have messed with a man's family.
我也这么跟你弟弟说的
I told your brother the same thing.
还加固了你的底盘
Reinforced your chassis.
看来我们是要来场负重赛了
It's like going into a ring with weighted gloves.
你错了
Your mistake.
我不是来小打小闹的
I'm not here to play games.
听着 我们俩是不同世界的人
See, you and me, we're from different worlds.
相信我 我见过很多比你更难缠的对手
Trust me, I've seen a lot meaner streets than the ones you're used to.
那多呆一会儿
Stick around.
事情会越来越难缠的
It's gonna get a lot meaner.
你以为我要跟你打一架吗？
You thought this was gonna be a street fight?
趴下
On the ground.
马上趴下！
Now!
放开他 不然我开枪了！
Drop him or I will drop you!
哇哦 哇哦 悠着点 伙计们 我们是一伙的
Whoa, whoa. Easy, guys. We're on the same team here.
托莱多先生
Mr. Toretto,
我们共同的伙伴推荐我来这地方
I'm here on the recommendation of a mutual friend of ours.
- 霍布斯先生 - 你他妈谁啊？
- Mr. Hobbs. - Who the hell are you?
我？我就是个人
Me? I'm just a guy.
我谁都不是
I'm Mr. Nobody.
小人物的话 这入场也太华丽了吧
It's a big entrance for a nobody.
那个害我们朋友进医院的家伙？
And the guy that put our mutual friend in the hospital?
你刚刚放跑他了
You just let him get away.
我觉得我刚刚是救了你一命 唐
I think I might have just saved your ass there, Dom.
话说 你能放开我的手下吗？
Listen, you think you could let go of my guy there?
他面色都有点发青了
He's beginning to turn a little blue.
我感谢你能这么做
I appreciate that.
搅局的来了
Ah, here they come.
听着 唐
Listen, Dom.
像我这种秘密人物之间有场战争
There's a war going on between shadows and ghosts like me.
你和你的团队在伦敦不知情地闯了进来
You and your team unwittingly walked into the middle of it in London,
看样子战火都烧到你家了
and it appears it's now followed you home.
你自己决定吧
It's up to you.
我先去喝一杯了
I'm gonna have a beer.
欢迎你加入我们
You're welcome to join me.
顺便一提 我可以找到德卡特·肖
By the way, I can get you Deckard Shaw.
（加州埃尔塞贡多 机密行动基地）
比利时艾尔啤酒
Belgian ale.
天啊 这群敲钟的做得太赞了
Oh, man, those monks got it right.
我的确不明白那什么独身主义
I mean, I don't know about the whole celibacy thing,
但说到啤酒…
but when it comes to beer…
你要来一杯吗？
Would you like one?
我跟喜欢喝科罗娜牌子
I'm more of a Corona man myself.
你的档案不止详尽
Your file's not only detailed,
还很有意思
it's, uh, extremely entertaining.
听着 肖的能力就是隐于无形
Look, Shaw's power is that he's a shadow.
他最拿手来无影去无踪
He's really good at getting in and out of places without being seen.
除了目标尸体 不留一丝痕迹
and leaving nothing but a body count in his wake.
他算是真正意义上的英国坏蛋
I mean, he's a legitimate English badass.
但说老实话 唐 我根本不在乎德卡特·肖
But to be honest with you, Dom, I don't give two shits about Deckard Shaw.
我要的是你
It's you I want.
因为你跟我互相帮助 最终就能各取所需
Because you and I can help each other get what we both need.
继续说下去
I'm listening.
最近一个通缉恐怖分子摩西·杰卡帝
Just recently a private military company.
领导的私人武装组织绑架了一个
led by a wanted terrorist named Mose Jakande.
名叫拉姆齐的黑客
kidnapped a hacker known only by the name "Ramsey."
美国这边对他很感兴趣 也应该如此
Now, Lady Liberty's got her panties in a bunch over this, but rightfully so,
因为拉姆齐发明了个有趣的东西
because this Ramsey has created something interesting.
- 放到大屏幕上 - 是 长官
- Bring it up. - Yes, Sir.
为你呈现
Say hello.
天眼系统
to God's Eye.
这小家伙可以黑入任何电子设备
Now, this little bastard hacks into anything that's on the digital network.
包括手机 卫星 自动取款机和电脑
That means every cell phone, satellite, ATM machine and computer.
还是同时完成
Simultaneously.
只要设备带有话筒或者镜头
If it's got a microphone or a lens,
天眼就能找到你
God's Eye can find you.
你带我来就是让我看个跟踪器
So you invited me here to show me a tracking device.
变态级的 而且数量众多
On steroids. Lots of them.
我就这么说吧
Let me put it to you this way.
我们花费了数年之久才找到奥萨马·本·拉登
It took us nearly a decade to find Osama bin Laden.
有这软件 不管他在地球上什么位置
With this, we'd have located him anywhere on the planet.
我们几小时就能找到他
in a couple of hours.
这是一件如果落在坏人手里
Now, that's a serious piece of machinery.
将会是一场大灾难的设备
that could be catastrophic in the wrong hands.
但由于某些可恶的政治原因
But for some very nauseating political reasons,
任何与美国政府势力或武装
any rescue plans involving.
相关的营救计划
any US government forces or entity.
完全不能执行
has been strictly ruled out.
这就是我需要你的原因
And that's why I need you.
但我为什么需要你呢？
But why do I need you?
我说 我可以出了这地方
I mean, I could go back outside,
享用剩下的科罗娜啤酒
enjoy the rest of the Coronas,
等肖来找我
let Shaw come to me.
你可以这么做 但到目前为止结果怎么样？
You could do that. How's that working out for you so far?
你的一个朋友死了 另一个在医院躺着
You got one friend in the ground, another one in the hospital.
当然了 还有炸弹炸毁了
And then, of course, there's that little issue of the bomb.
你房子的小问题
that destroyed your home.
肖所生活的世界 规矩
Shaw lives in a world that doesn't.
和你的不同
play by your rules.
不管你愿不愿意
Like it or not,
你现在也在那个世界中了
you live in that world now, too.
你想知道怎么杀死一个影子吗？
You wanna know how to kill a shadow?
只需要给他打一点光
You just shine a little light on it.
如果你帮我拿到天眼
If you get the God's Eye for me,
我已经得到授权
I've already got authorization.
可以给你使用 直到找到肖
for you to use it until you get Shaw.
你从猎物变成了猎人
You go from the hunted to the hunter.
地球上不会有任何地方可以让肖躲过你
And there's no place on Earth Shaw can hide from you.
更重要的是
More importantly,
你和你的家人不用再去参加任何葬礼了
you and your family don't go to any more funerals.
你找到了拉姆齐 就找到了天眼
You get Ramsey, you get the God's Eye,
也就找到了肖
you get Shaw.
好了 我的球已经投出了
Well, that's the wind-up and the pitch.
我给了你如此敏感
Now that I've given you this incredibly sensitive.
且高度机密的消息 你怎么想 托莱多？
and highly classified information, what do you think, Toretto?
我想你已经知道我会怎么做了
I think you already know what I'm gonna do.
很好
Good.
但得用我的方式
But it'll be my way.
和我的人
And my crew.
我猜到你会这么说
I assumed you might say that.
这也就是我召集了你队伍的原因
Which is why I've taken the liberty of gathering your team.
这太疯狂了
This is crazy.
这儿是要干什么呀？
What the hell is going on in here?
我们的智囊团认为
Our intelligence suggests that Ramsey.
拉姆齐会被武装车队转移
will be transported by an armed motorcade.
通过高加索山脉
through the Caucasus mountain range.
如果他们通过山脉到达目的地
If they clear this range and reach their destination,
就再也别想找到她了
Ramsey is as good as gone.
所以我说得直接点
So let me get this straight.
只有一条路可以进出
There's only one road that leads in or out,
周边都是悬崖峭壁
sheer drops on every side,
这该死的车队周围任何方向一公里范围内
a motorcade from hell protected by a small army.
都有军队严密保护？
from one mile in either direction?
是的 就是这样
Yeah, that's about it.
- 你说完了？- 不 没说完
- You done? - No, I'm not done.
你们希望我闯入
So you all wanted me to break into.
一所警察局 好的
a police station. Fine.
接着你们又让我阻止一辆坦克
Then you asked me to stop a tank.
我不是太高兴 但我还是做了
I wasn't happy about it, but I did it.
接着你们想出这绝妙的主意
Then you came up with this brilliant idea.
打下一架史上最大的飞机
to shoot down one of the largest airplanes ever.
我把那该死的玩意儿轰出了天空
I shot that shit out of the sky. Mmm.
这没什么
It's nothing.
但这个 我的朋友们
But this right here, my friend,
正好是
happens to be.
我这辈子听到的最愚蠢的主意
the stupidest idea I've ever heard of in my life.
我忘了原来飞机是你一个人打下来的
I forgot that you were the only one to bring the plane down.
不 不 我唯一看到他打下的东西
No, no. The only thing I've ever seen him take down was.
是没膝盖的丹尼斯
"No Knees" Denise.
记得吗？舞会那个
Remember, at prom?
真的吗 布莱恩？你要在这里这样？
Really, Brian? You're gonna do that right here?
看到了吧 你们所有人就想打乱我的思路
See, y'all trying to get me off my point.
我说的是 我厌倦了让我身边的所有人
All I'm saying is, I'm tired of everybody around me.
决定所有的事
making all the decisions.
这次 我来领队
This time, I lead.
严肃点 如果不能让我做决定的话 我退出
Seriously. If I don't start making decisions, I'm out.
好的 罗曼
All right, Roman.
你有什么想法？
What do you got?
我不是想立即立刻全面领导什么的
I mean, I wasn't trying to get into the whole leadership thing, like, now.
懂我的意思吗？
You know what I'm saying?
我就是想说总有个时刻得让我拍板
I was just, kind of, talking about, like, at some point.
比如 你知道的 当我们…
Like, you know, when we…
无论如何 我是说 我想…
Whatever. I mean, I think…
我们从这里攻击
Let's hit it from here.
- 我不认为那里… - 别 别 别 别思考
- I don't think that that's… - No, no, no, don't think.
这是我的工作
That's my job.
好
Okay.
从这里攻击是不可能的
It is impossible to hit it there.
这里堪称是山上最安全的地方
That is literally the most secure spot on the mountain.
为什么？因为你根本到不了这里
Why? Because you cannot physically access it.
看到了吧 这就是这里的优势
See, that's what makes it so sweet.
因为这是他们最不会防备我们攻击的地方
Because it's the place that they least expect us to hit them from.
尽管我不想承认 他似乎说到了点子上
As much as I hate to admit it, he's onto something there.
你觉得呢 唐？
What do you think, Dom?
- 这里？- 是的
- Here? - Yeah.
我想我们有计划了
I think we got a plan.
完全错误的想法
Completely wrong thinking.
但我喜欢
And I like it.
看到了吧？我很擅长做这个
You see? I'm good at this.
「擅长」？好的
"Good"? Okay.
你怎么计划到达那条路上呢？
How are you planning on getting on that road?
好啦 特吉？
Well, Tej?
关于这点 我可能真的有计划了
I think I may actually have a plan for that.
怎么了？我分工了 一个好的领导就要这么做
What? I delegated. That's what good leaders do.
领导！
Leader!
当我看你的档案时
You know, when I was reading your files,
你和你的队伍做到的事情给我很深的印象
I was impressed with what you've accomplished with your team.
但现在见到了他们 我必须说 唐
But meeting them now, I've gotta say, Dom,
你真的有一种天赋
you've truly got a gift.
把我的车间当成你新的玩具厂吧
Consider my workshop your new playhouse.
我会发现我们的车非常吸引人
I think you'll find our cars extremely appealing.
你的队伍现在齐了
And your team is now complete.
我去了家里
I went to the house.
我到处找你
I was looking for you everywhere.
你吓死我了
You scared the shit out of me.
你不会再一个人了 不管你去哪…
You will never be alone. Wherever you go…
不要告诉别人
Tell no one.
你在哪里找到的？
Where did you find that?
在韩的车里
Found in Han's car.
被人当成留言故意留下
It was left as a message.
我打算好好「回报」他
A message I plan on returning.
你可以开车吗？
Can you ride?
当然可以
Yeah, of course I can.
韩也是我的家人
Han was my family, too.
布莱恩！
Brian!
每辆车上都要装越野避震器
We're gonna need long-travel suspension,
还有限滑差速器
limited-slip differentials on all of them.
你还好吗？
How you doing?
特吉！
Tej!
我要你把这辆车的优点和那辆的
I want the demon love child between that.
结合起来
and that.
这有很多的防护钢板
That's a lot of armor.
会增加车体重量
It's just gonna add more weight.
减慢速度
Slow you down.
这次要的不仅仅是速度
This time, it ain't just about being fast.
是的 我很厉害
Yeah, I'm good.
当初混大街的时候 你知道我在说什么吗？
From the streets. You know what I'm saying?
没事的
It's nothing.
嘿 罗曼 你吓死了对吧？
Hey, Roman, you're freaking out, ain't you?
- 没有 - 有的
- No. - Yeah, you are.
我说了没有
I said no.
听着 伙计 一个成熟的人能接受自己的感受
Listen, man, it takes a grown man to embrace his feelings.
如果你想哭 就哭出来吧
If you need to cry, just go ahead and cry.
作为你的朋友 你知道我很关心你的健康
As your friend, you know I'm concerned about your well-being,
所以我提前做了预防
which is why I took the precaution.
放了成人尿不湿在你的副驾抽屉里
of putting some adult diapers in your glove compartment.
你可以闭嘴吗 伙计？
Yo, can you just chill out, man?
我见过许多疯狂的事 唐
I have seen some crazy shit, Dom,
但这个真的算是高潮了
but this really could make some waves.
所以我们尽可能的保持低调 好吗？
So let's just try to keep it as low-key as possible, huh?
我不是一直如此吗？
Don't I always?
我告诉你 你这次要能搞定了
I'll tell you what, you knock it down a couple of notches this time.
我会把我的比利时啤酒换成一桶科罗娜
and I'll swap out my Belgian for a keg of Corona.
那你是给自己做了件好事
You'd be doing yourself a favor, there.
有人可以跟我说说我们要干什么吗？
Can somebody just walk me through what we're supposed to be doing?
得了吧 罗曼 这是你的计划 你要接受它
Come on, Rom, this is your plan. You gotta embrace it.
不 这不是我的计划
No, this was not my plan.
好了 开始了 游戏时间到
Oh, yeah, here we go. Game time.
罗曼 你不是需要新鲜空气吗？
Roman, you need some fresh air?
因为马上你就能吸到很多了
Because you're about to get a whole lot of it.
好了 出发！
Okay, here we go!
就在你以为不能更好的时候对吧？
Just when you didn't think it could get any better, huh?
该死的！
Oh, shit!
哇呜！
Whoo!
这样就顺畅了
Now we're moving.
大家都好吗？大家都出来了吗？
Everybody good? Everybody make it out?
你就是没有告诉他们你干不了这个！
You just didn't tell them that this is not for you!
这不是你的任务！
This is not your mission!
罗曼？怎么了 伙计？和我说话 快点！
Hey, Rom? Hey, what's up, man? Talk to me, come on!
- 我做不到 - 去你妹的做不到！
- I can't do it. - The hell you can't!
拜托 伙计！你把那东西
Come on, man! You throw that thing.
切到倒车档 赶紧给我出来！
in reverse and get your ass out here now!
听着 我做不到 好吗？听听我在说什么
Look, I can't do it, okay? Listen to what I'm saying.
现在不是时候！
Now isn't the time!
我要和飞行员一起待在这里
I'ma stay up here with the pilot.
我们会在附近一带盘旋
We gonna circle around and make sure.
确保你们在下面没事！
we holding it down from up here!
你快没时间了！
You're running out of time!
降落伞是用GPS导航的！
The chute is guided by GPS!
你什么都不用做！
You don't have to do anything!
- 特吉！- 我来解决
- Tej! - I'm already on it.
嘿 伙计们 听着
Hey, man, listen.
我很抱歉让你们失望了 好吗？
I'm sorry to let y'all down, okay?
我就待在这里了
I'ma go ahead and stay up here.
不 兄弟
No, brother.
- 我很抱歉要让你失望了 - 什么？
- I'm sorry to let you down. - What?
你什么意思 你要…
What do you mean you're…
特吉！你在干什么？
Tej! What are you doing?
该死！
Oh, shit!
特吉！
Tej!
我恨你 特吉！
I hate you, Tej!
准备！
Get ready!
马上就要着陆了！
Ground's coming fast!
加油 宝贝 加油
Come on, baby. Come on.
爽！
Oh, yeah!
触底得分！
Touchdown, baby!
车辆检查 汇报
Car check. Call it in.
- 正常 - 正常
- Check. - Check.
我很好 我们动手吧
I'm good. Let's do this.
喂？求你们了 来个人把我弄出去！
Hello? Please, man. Get me out of here, somebody!
不！那些树！
No! The trees!
该死
Oh, shit.
坐好了 罗曼 我们会回来找你的
Sit tight, Roman. We'll come back for you.
计划不是这样的！
This is not the plan!
（阿塞拜疆 高加索山脉）
好了 你只有一次救人的机会 唐
All right, you got one chance to hit them here, Dom.
失手的话 他们就会回到秘密基地
You miss, they'll make it to their black site.
然后从拉姆齐嘴里撬出他们需要的一切情报
and they'll squeeze whatever information they need out of Ramsey.
你再也没机会拿到装置 也没机会抓到肖了
The device and your chance of ever getting Shaw will be gone for good.
这不可能
That ain't gonna happen.
我们汇合点见
I'll see you at the pickup.
拉姆齐应该在客车上
Ramsey will be in the bus.
那就开工吧
Then let's do this.
队长 有人来了 有四辆车在接近
Captain, we have company. Four cars, inbound.
该死！
Oh, shit!
- 特吉 掩护！- 我来了
- Tej, shield! - I'm on the way.
好了 排队形
All right, formation.
防弹的 宝贝
Bulletproof, baby.
你打不穿
Can't touch this.
撞上去！
Punch it!
干得好！哈哈！
Strike! Ha-ha!
启动机枪
Guns free.
不！
No!
快躲开！
Get out of the way!
那些不是枪 那些根本就是机关炮！
Those aren't guns, those are goddamn cannons!
都是装甲弹！
Armor-piercing rounds!
发射抓钩
Hook them up.
布莱恩 特吉 引爆炸弹！
Brian, Tej, blow it!
扯掉它
Lock it up.
布莱恩 该你了
Brian, you're up.
再近一点 特吉！
Little closer, Tej!
拉姆齐？
Ramsey?
离我远点！退后！别碰我！
Stay away from me! Stay back! Don't you touch me!
我是布莱恩 我会把你救出去的
My name's Brian. I'm gonna get you out of here.
但请你冷静 好吧？
but I'm gonna need you to settle down, all right?
我来把绑你的带子切开
I'm gonna cut those things off of you.
长官？
Sir?
长官 有一辆不明车辆靠近
Sir, we have an unidentified vehicle approaching.
快点！再近点！
Come on! Closer!
- 你必须跳上去 - 不！不！不！
- You're gonna have to jump. - No! No! No!
没时间了！快点！
We don't have time! Come on!
- 我们要离开这里 - 快点
- We gotta get out of here. - Come on.
- 看着我！看着我！- 我不跳！
- Look at me! Look at me! - I'm not jumping!
你不跳的话 我们都得死 知道吗？
You don't jump, we're gonna die. Okay?
你必须跳 来吧！
You're jumping. Come on!
一
One.
二！
Two!
好啊 好啊
Well, well, well.
抓住我的手！
Take my hand!
欢迎加入 肖先生
Welcome to the party, Mr. Shaw.
莱蒂 你跟着布莱恩
Letty, stay with Brian.
该死！
Oh, shit!
你在干嘛？这也太疯狂了！
What are you doing? This is crazy!
让你活命
Keeping you alive.
那里有悬崖 悬崖！
There's a cliff. Cliff!
悬崖！那里有悬崖！
Cliff! There's a cliff!
该死！
Shit!
太慢了
Too slow.
耶！
Yeah!
我回来了 贱人们！
I'm back, bitches!
你没事吧？
You good?
谢谢
Thank you.
- 罗曼 去找其他人 - 你呢？
- Roman, get back to the others. - What about you?
不用担心我
Don't worry about me.
不得不说 你让我印象深刻
I have to say, I am impressed.
我很想知道是谁
I would very much like to know the name of the man.
给我制造了这么多麻烦
who is causing me so much trouble.
那里没路了
There's no way out of there.
他在干嘛？
What is he doing?
他就像被困在车灯前的鹿
He's frozen like a damn deer in headlights.
托莱多才不是鹿
Toretto ain't no deer.
加油 多米尼克
Come on, Dominic.
交出那个女孩 就给你活路
Give us the girl, and I'll let you live.
你打算怎么做？
What are you going to do?
这回你也许要戴上头盔了
You might wanna put on your helmet for this one.
头…
Helm…
瞄准司机
Target the driver.
见鬼！他在想什么？
Damn it! What is he thinking?
你疯了吧！
You're insane!
你的方向错了
You're pointing the wrong way.
是吗？
Am I now?
听我的命令开枪
Fire on my mark.
- 有意思 - 三！
- Interesting. - Three!
- 二！- 抓紧
- Two! - Hold on.
一！
One!
开火！
Fire!
看起来我们的恶魔混血儿成功了
Looks like our demon love child worked.
这也算是下山的路
That's one way down a mountain.
拉姆齐在哪里？
Where's Ramsey?
小猫咪醒了
Hello Kitty is awake.
我觉得她看起来不像是黑客
She don't look like a hacker to me.
是吗？你觉得黑客长什么样子？
Oh, yeah? And what do hackers look like?
他们不应该长那样
They don't supposed to look like that.
我只是说说 你知道他们通常戴着小小的歪歪扭扭
I'm just saying, like, you know how they normally wear them little,
奇奇怪怪的眼镜
weird glasses that's all crooked,
还有喝苏打水长出来满脸的小脓包？
and pimples all over their face from drinking soda?
我意思是 相信我 有那样的身材
I mean, trust me, with a body like that,
你才不会甘心蹲在电脑后面
you ain't gonna park it behind a computer.
感觉怎样？
How are you feeling?
撞到头了吗？
Did you hit your head?
感觉恶心吗？耳鸣？没有？
Feeling nauseous? Ears ringing? No?
我的鞋呢？
Where's my shoe?
你坠地时飞了
Oh, it flew off when you crashed.
如果你开始感觉到刚才的那些症状 告诉我 好吗？
If you start experiencing any of those things, let me know, okay?
我不知道是该谢谢你们救我
I don't know whether to thank you for rescuing me.
还是应该因为你们把我扔下悬崖而揍你们一顿
or kick your ass for throwing me off a cliff.
表示感谢还是揍一顿？
Thank us or kick our ass, huh?
要不你告诉我们装置在哪里吧？
How about you tell us where that device is?
我寄给一个朋友了
I mailed it to a friend.
在阿布扎比
In Abu Dhabi.
这很容易嘛
That was pretty easy.
之前那队人本来会为了这个折磨你的
That other team would have tortured you for that information.
我不信任他们 我相信你们
I didn't trust them. I trust you.
那你为什么相信我们？你都不认识我们
Now, why would you trust us? You barely know us.
我知道得足够多了
I know enough.
前任警察 或者军人等类似的职业
Ex-cop. Military, something like that.
从你对付他们的手法能看得出接受过训练
The way you took out them guys shows training.
技术男 别人对黑客的评论自然也冒犯了他
Tech guy, offended by the hacker remark, naturally.
大哥
Alpha.
大嫂
Mrs. Alpha.
逗乐的人
Joker.
错
Wrong.
也是大哥
Double alpha.
美男子 知道什么意思吗？
Man candy. You know what I'm saying?
哥们 你他妈给我坐下吧
Man, sit your candy ass down.
真是不尊重
The disrespect is real around here.
生活是二次元 不是零就是一
Life is binary. Zeroes and ones.
只有两样东西能让这样的团队聚在一起
Only two things keep a group like this together.
害怕或忠诚
Fear or loyalty.
在你们当中我没看到一丝害怕
And I don't see a drop of fear among you guys.
非常精彩 但有一件事
Very impressive. Just one thing.
他们没结婚
They're not married.
她错得太离谱了 这也不对吧 你就这样放任吗？
She's so off, it's crazy. You just gonna roll with it?
你是说一队里不能有两个老大吗？
You're telling me there can't be a double alpha in one group?
你们为美国政府工作？
You work for US government?
我们有共同利益
We got similar interests.
特吉 打电话
Tej, call it in.
我们要去中东了！
We're going to the Middle East!
嘿
Hey.
嘿 唐 在山上可真够狂野的 对吧？
Hey, Dom. It was pretty wild on that mountain, huh?
不 那太悬了
No, it was too close.
但我们完成了任务
But we got the job done.
你知道疯狂的是…
You know what the crazy thing is, is…
你怀念子弹
You miss the bullets.
是 一团糟 是吧？
Yeah, that's messed up, huh?
布莱恩 我见过你跳下火车 从飞机上跳海
Brian, I've seen you jump from trains, dive from planes.
天啊 我见你的那天就看出了你的勇气
Hell, I saw your courage the day I met you.
是啊
Right.
想知道我见你做过的最勇敢的事吗？
Want to know the bravest thing I ever saw you do?
做米娅的好丈夫
Be a good man to Mia.
做我侄子杰克的好父亲
Being a great father to my nephew, Jack.
大家都在寻找刺激
Everyone's looking for the thrill,
但唯一真实的是家庭
but what's real is family.
你的家庭
Your family.
记住这一点 布莱恩
Hold on to that, Brian.
（阿拉伯联合酋长国 阿布扎比）
比我想象的要热多了
It's hotter than I thought it would be.
是啊 我们在沙漠 当然热了
Yeah, well, we are in the desert, so it would be hot.
不 我说的不是天气
Oh, no, I ain't talking about the weather.
- 天啊 天啊 - 嗯
- My, my, my. - Hmm.
这个女人
Now, that is a woman.
值得你从飞机上跳下来
that's worth falling out a plane for.
一边去 伙计 我先下了饵
Get out of there, man, I got dibs on that.
你看到我在看了
You've seen me looking at that.
你说「下饵」？
Did you just say "dibs"?
你多大啦 四年级吗？
What are you, in the fourth grade?
伙计 你能走开吗？
Man, can you just get out of there?
我是说得自由竞争
I mean, it's a free market.
你在说什么呢？走开
What are you talking about? Get out of there.
我们剪刀 石头 布 赢的人约她
Rock, paper, scissors for her.
你们是玩真的吗？
Are you guys for real right now?
看看你们
Look at you.
你们看上去都被俘获了
You both look whupped already.
眼神都和跟踪狂一样
You got stalker eyes.
两年前 我试着钓拉姆齐
I tried to call dibs on Ramsey two years ago.
她的膝盖对我的蛋蛋
Her knee, my balls.
相信我 你们不会想要的
Trust me, you don't wanna do that.
嘿！拉姆齐！
Hey! Ramsey!
你好 沙法
Hello, Safar.
我看到你交了新朋友
I see you make some new friends.
没错 一些毛躁的新朋友
Yeah, some short-tempered new friends.
我需要之前寄给你的快速驱动盘 它在哪？
I need the speed drive I sent you. Where is it?
很好 你要是知道我把它卖了 一定很高兴
Oh, good. You will be pleased to know I sold it.
你把它卖了？
You sold it?
听到没？
You hear that?
我叫你好好保管
I asked you to take care of it.
你为什么要卖了？
Why on earth would you sell it?
我们要拿回来
We're gonna need it back.
不可能
Impossible.
沙法 我在里面藏了些东西 这很重要
Safar, I stashed something inside it. It's important.
好的 好的
Okay, okay.
好消息是 它很安全
Uh, good news. It is safe.
坏消息呢？
And the bad news?
安全过头了
It is very safe.
我把它卖给了一个住在那上面的约旦王子
I sold it to a Jordanian prince living up there.
亿万信托基金的富家子
Trust fund billionaire.
他说想把它用在他的超级跑车上
Said he wanted to use it for his supercar.
听到了吗？
Now, see, this?
这个我喜欢
This, I like.
亿万富翁 超级跑车…
Billionaire, supercar…
那车有什么过人之处？
What makes it so super?
最高时速两百四十二英里
242 miles per hour, top speed.
它还防弹
And it's bulletproof.
两百四十二…
242…
这里只有我一个人亢奋了吗？
Am I the only one aroused right now?
就像 你知道我什么意思吗？
It's, like, you know what I'm saying?
算了
Whatever.
他车放哪里了？
Where does he keep it?
在他的顶层公寓
In his penthouse.
一号塔
Tower number one.
为什么他要把车停在顶楼？
Now, why in the hell would he keep his car in his penthouse?
他是亿万富翁 朋友
He's a billionaire, my friend.
爱干嘛就干嘛
He can do whatever he wants.
明天刚好是一年中白昼最长的一天
Now, tomorrow happens to be the longest day of the year.
王子要在下午开个派对庆祝一下
The prince wants to celebrate it and host a party tomorrow afternoon.
你帮我们混进去 没问题吧？
So you can get us up there, right?
当然了
Sure.
但是 呃 穿成这样可不行
But, uh, not dressed like that.
怎么了？
What?
哪儿不对劲吗？
Is something wrong?
太多烦心事了
There's a billion things wrong.
但绝不是此刻应该考虑的
But not in this moment.
你今天很帅
You look handsome.
我都有点不好意思了
I feel awkward.
我也是
You and me both.
你今天的打扮
Just seeing you dressed like this.
让我想起了一些事
just reminds me of something.
什么？
Of what?
过去
Old times.
你还好吗？
You okay?
当然 没问题
Yeah. I'm fine.
好戏开场了
Showtime.
不 不 不 听着 伙计
No, no, no. Listen, man.
他们跟我说他们每天都开派对
They're telling me they party like this every day.
在这个楼层 每天都这么嗨
On this level, they party every day.
太疯狂了 我应该搬到这儿来
This is crazy. I might have to move out here.
我觉得我要引领一个新潮流了 就叫做Blarab
I think I'm gonna start a new culture. It's called Blarab.
你知道的 听起来像「阿拉伯黑人」
You know, like "black Arab."
特吉 进展如何？
How are we looking, Tej?
我们马上就到了
We're almost in position.
好了 流程是这样的
Okay, so this is how it works.
我们必须得同时进去 才有可能的手
We got to move in sync if we're gonna pull this off.
所以我们顺一遍 确保
So let's go over it to make sure.
大家都清楚自己的任务
everyone clearly understands their roles.
罗曼 说给你听的
Roman, that means you.
你知道吗 你现在越来越不专业了 特吉
You know what, you're being real unprofessional right now, Tej.
天眼芯片藏在驱动盘里
The God's Eye chip is hidden in a speed drive.
驱动盘在王子的车里 而车在保险库里
installed in the prince's car, which he keeps in a safe room vault.
这里大概有8到10个便衣保安
I make 8 to 10 plainclothes security.
更别说还有王子本人
Not to mention the prince.
和他的私人保镖了
and his personal bodyguards.
摄像头密布北墙 保险库就在那儿
Security cameras are clustered by the north wall. That's where the vault is.
我们得先进入保险库 然后黑进安全系统
We got to get in that vault, we got to tap into the security system,
才能进入王子的卧室
which can be accessed in the prince's bedroom.
好吧 伙计们 我要进去了
All right, guys, I'm going in.
打扰了
Excuse me.
噢 我只是在找…
Oh, I was just looking for the…
- 派对在那个方向 - 什么？
- The party is that way. - What?
此房间禁止入内
This room is off-limits.
现在 一旦我们进入了安全系统
Now, once we're tapped in,
拉姆齐和我就能黑进他们的网络把门打开
Ramsey and I can hack into the network and pop the door.
然后你们就能进去拿货了
so you can get in and get that shit.
等等 等等 你漏掉我了
Wait, wait, wait. You missed a step.
你忘了我吗？我应该做什么？
What about my steps? What am I supposed to be doing?
没有 计划就是这样
No, we didn't miss anything.
你们是一支特殊的队伍 所以当我们需要你的时候
You're special teams. So when we need you,
做你最擅长的事就行
do what you do best.
那是什么？
And that is?
完美展现罗曼·皮尔斯的魅力
Shine brightly like only Roman Pearce can do.
哈哈
Ha-ha.
看见没？我们也能愉快地对话
See? Now we talking.
好了 特吉 我进来了
All right, Tej, I'm in.
好的 找到电话接口
All right, find the phone jack.
连接线一般都在那个后面
The tap always runs behind that.
那儿会有一个350兆赫的超五类电缆
It's gonna be a 350-megahertz CAT5e cable.
接口后面会有许多根线
They probably got a couple dozen back there,
你需要找到有充气外壳的那根
but this will be the bonded pair with the plenum coat.
说人话 特吉
English, Tej.
就是橙色的那根
It'll be the orange wire.
好了 女士们先生们 我们已经进入安全系统了
All right, ladies and gentlemen, we are in the pilot seat.
好吧 罗曼
All right, Roman.
展现你的魅力把
Do whatever it is you do.
今天是你的生日 对不对？
It's your birthday, right?
你是茉莉吧？
Are you Jasmine?
- 天啊 不 别来生日这套啊 - 把手给我
- Oh, God, no. Not the birthday routine. - Take my hand.
祝你生日快乐 这边 过来这里
Happy birthday to you. This way, this way.
不好意思 让一下 我得过去 抱歉
Excuse me, so sorry. I'm coming through, sorry.
过来这边 各位 请给我一分钟的时间
Right this way. Listen, excuse me one second.
天啊 天啊 哥们 你不能…
My brother, my brother. Man, you ain't supposed to…
谢谢你 先生
Sir, thank you so much.
好了 请听我说句话 朋友们 请过来这边
All right, listen, people. Please, everybody, gather around.
理解一下 谢谢了
Understand something, right now.
接下来我要宣布一件事情
Listen to what I'm telling y'all.
今天是茉莉十八岁的生日
We are here to celebrate Jasmine's 18th birthday.
生日快乐 亲爱的
Happy birthday, my dear.
∮ 祝你生日 ∮
∮ Happy birthday to you ∮
∮ 快乐 ∮
∮ To you ∮
噢 真是不忍直视
Oh, I wish I didn't see that.
拉姆齐 帮我们开门
Ramsey, open it up for us.
收到 可以进去了
Copy that. You're in.
你能想象吗？
Do you realize what this is?
Lykan HyperSport超跑
Lykan HyperSport.
三百四十万美元
$3.4 million.
3秒之内提速到60迈
Zero-to-60 in less than three seconds.
全球限量7台
There's seven of these things in the world,
可是这个王子却把它锁在了保险库里
and this guy keeps it locked up in a vault.
再没有什么比困兽更可悲的事情了
Nothing's sadder than locking a beast in a cage.
现在我真想给他一拳
And now I really want to punch him in the face.
好了
Okay.
开始工作吧
Let's get to work.
你能撑得住吧？
You got this, right?
快点
Go.
要是我说他只是被魅力迷倒的 你会相信吗？
Would you believe I knocked him out with my charm?
你可没有那个魅力 臭婊子
You ain't that charming, bitch.
（发现入侵者）
（关闭系统）
特吉 你的小把戏不管用了 我们没法控制系统了
Tej, your magic trick is failing. We're losing systems.
我知道
I know.
我看见了
I see it.
特吉 说话
Tej, talk to me.
我正在努力 但是他们的安全系统把我们锁在外面了
I'm trying, but their security system is locking us out.
好吧 请听我说 女士们先生们…
All right, listen, ladies and gentlemen…
噢 王子来了 这是你们的舞者吗？
Oh, there he is. These are your dancers?
这可是个派对 嗨起来 宝贝！
This is a party, baby!
你们或许该去卫生间
Some of y'all probably went to the bathroom.
看看是不是发胶都不见了
and noticed that all the hairspray was missing.
没错 就是她用的
Yep. She did it.
谢谢
Thank you.
你能来我们实在是太高兴了
And we're so happy for you to be here.
看来你的裙底藏了不少杀伤性武器 对不对？
You look like you got some missiles underneath that dress. No?
他没有… 你还真说了吗？
He did not just… Did you just say that?
该死！别把门关了！别把门关了！
Oh, shit! Not the gate! Not the gate!
布莱恩 快点！
Brian, faster!
我们已经竭尽全力了
We're playing all the defense we can up here.
但没用 你们动作快点
but we're gonna lose. You gotta hurry up.
谢天谢地你出现了
Thank God you showed up.
派对简直无聊死了
These parties bore me to death.
伙计们 你们得马上离开
Guys, get out of there right now.
王子调来了军队来对付你们
You've got an army heading your way.
布莱恩 快出来！别搞了！
Brian, get out! Forget it!
特吉 我们直接把车带走
Tej, we're taking the car.
我天生就这样 你知道我在说什么吗？一旦我…
This is what I do. You know what I'm saying? As far as I'm…
天啊 这…
My man, what's…
莱蒂？
Letty?
莱蒂 说话 你还好吗？
Letty, talk to me. Are you okay?
伙计们 我撑不住了 最后一扇门也要关闭了
Guys, I can't hold it. I'm losing the final gate.
你们必须马上撤离
You gotta get out of there.
冲出去！别管他们
Tear out the dash! Go through it.
等等 等等 冷静点 伙计
Wait, wait, wait. Now, just hold on, man.
是时候让野兽出笼了
Time to unleash the beast.
我们走！
Let's go!
跟着我 我来保护你
Stay with me, I got you.
我们离开这里
Let's get the hell out of here.
唐 车可不会飞！
Dom, cars don't fly!
车不会飞！
Cars don't fly!
天啊！
Holy shit!
- 刹车坏了！- 什么？
- No brakes! - What?
- 刹车坏了！- 该死！
- No brakes! - Shit!
不 不 不！
No, no, no!
不！
No!
噢！
Oh!
- 拿到了！- 快下车！
- Got it! - Get out!
你还想念子弹吗 布莱恩？
Still miss the bullets, Brian?
- 啊！破坏王们回来了 - 抱歉
- Ah! There they are. Disaster. - I'm sorry.
我把你们弄进了阿布扎比最高级的派对
I get you an invite to the most exclusive party in Abu Dhabi.
- 沙法… - 别废话 我不听
- Safar… - No, no, no.
你们不仅偷了车 还开着在两栋楼之间飞来飞去
You steal the host's car, and you jump it between two buildings.
- 其实是三栋楼 - 噢！
- Actually, it was three buildings. - Oh!
还嫌委屈了 三栋很值得骄傲吗
Two, insult. Three, honor.
我的错
My bad.
好样的
Well, well, well.
不得不说
I have to say,
您对「低调」的理解还真是独特 托莱多先生
you've got an interesting interpretation there of "low-key, " Mr. Toretto.
要知道 唐 我以为我们已经达成共识了
You know, Dom, I thought we had an understanding.
有时候你不得不改变下游戏规则
Sometimes you have to play the hand you're dealt.
这就是为什么我更愿意做庄家
That's why I prefer to be the dealer.
晚安
Good night.
我被人从自己的车库赶出去 真有你们的
I'm being kicked out of my own garage. This is great.
我能看下吗？
Uh, may I?
布莱恩
Brian,
给他吧
give it to him.
费了这么大劲 都只是为了这么一个
All that trouble for this little.
小玩意
thing.
恕我直言 唐
With all due respect, Dom,
你实在是太厉害了
you really did great work back there.
你们都很棒
All of you.
我的所有手下都在待命
All of my men are now standing by.
完全听你差遣了
and are fully at your disposal.
你来指挥
Your call.
拉姆齐
Ramsey.
启动它 帮我找到肖
Fire it up and find me Shaw.
天啊 太激动人心了
Oh, damn, this is crazy.
谢谢
Thank you.
好吧 给我点时间
All right, give me a second.
它在干什么？
What is it doing now?
搜寻中
It's hunting.
黑进阿提哈德塔保安系统的摄像头
Hacking into the security cameras at Etihad Towers.
那是你最后一次看到肖的地方 我们从那儿入手
That's the last place you saw Shaw, so that's where we'll start.
那是他 就在那儿
That's him, right there.
等等 这些数字是干什么的？
Wait, wait. What are these numbers right here for?
它正在用生物技术识别肖的脸
It's bio-mapping Shaw's face.
然后在这个半球的所有探头录像
It'll run it against every camera.
和所有音频设备中搜索
Every audio device in this hemisphere.
找到了 他应该藏在这里
Bingo. Looks like he's holed up here.
不二选择
That's perfect.
自动化工厂 没有人 遍地都是藏身之处
Automated factory, no people, lots of places to hide.
你永久性地改变了搜寻方式
You just changed the face of manhunts forever.
恭喜
Congratulations.
嘿 我能看下邮箱吗 很快的？
Hey, can I check my email real quick?
再过两个小时就天亮了
Dawn's up in two hours.
天一亮我们就去干掉肖
We're gonna go take down Shaw then.
去准备吧
Go get changed.
我们得出发了
We should go now.
就你和你的手下 还有我
Just you, your team, and me.
我以为你说要等到天亮
I thought you said at dawn.
我的朋友们是赛车手
My guys are racers,
世界一流的赛车手
the best drivers in the world.
但他们不是杀手
But they ain't killers.
我就说 他会那么说的
Told you he'd say that.
我太了解你了 唐 所以我要和你一起去
I know you too well, Dom, and I'm going with you.
好吧 看起来我们要开个抓捕派对了
Well, looks like we got a nice little hunting party.
我们去抓那只影子吧
Let's go bag a shadow.
还有十公里 兄弟们 准备出动
Ten klicks out, boys. Get ready to rock and roll.
我们到了 打开武器保险
Here we go. Weapons hot.
- 你准备好了吗？- 当然
- You ready for this? - Yeah.
希望你的最后一餐吃得愉快
I hope you're enjoying your last meal.
就这么点人？
This is it?
我只值你们派这些人来？
This is all I warrant?
才十几个人？
A dozen men?
我会让你觉得这人数绰绰有余的
I think you'll find it's more than enough.
我已经做好去见造物主的准备了
I'm ready to meet my maker.
你呢？
Are you?
你想什么呢 托莱多？想要偷袭我？
What were you expecting, Toretto? To catch me off guard?
期待我站在这里 挥舞着白旗投降？
Me standing here, waving a white flag?
你难道没听过一句话叫
You ever heard the saying,
“敌人的敌人
"The enemy of my enemy.
是我的朋友？”
is my friend?"
我没有朋友
I don't have friends.
我只有家人
I got family.
我可有很多朋友
Well, I got a lot of friends.
两人阵型！谢帕德 跟着我！
Two-two formation! Sheppard, peel one!
布莱恩 别管它了！
Brian, leave it!
卧倒！
Get down!
有我在
I got you.
天眼系统
God's Eye.
你该不会真以为我什么防备都没做就冲进去了吧？
You didn't really think I was gonna walk in there naked, did you?
你伤得很重
You got hit bad.
听着 托莱多
Look, Toretto.
我知道你不会照我说的去做
I know you won't listen to me.
你不会喜欢我接下来要说的话
You're not gonna want to hear what I have to say.
但事实是
But the truth is,
你真的应该
you really ought to.
尝尝艾尔啤酒 真的
try that Belgian ale, man.
它很特别
It's something special.
艾尔啤酒 是吗？
Belgian ale, huh?
嘿 我们必须送你去医院
Hey, we gotta get you to a hospital.
不 别送我去
No, you're not.
我随身带着保命的东西
I carry my own health insurance.
紧急医疗队早就在待命了 他们已经赶来了
SOCM medics on standby. They're already inbound.
靠边停吧 年轻人
Pull over, kid.
唐 你一定要保护拉姆齐
Dom, you gotta protect Ramsey.
只要她活着
As long as she's alive,
她就能把他们从天眼系统踢出来 他们也知道这点
she can lock them out of God's Eye, and they know that.
这意味着不抓到她 他们是绝对不会罢休的
That means they're not gonna stop coming until they've got her.
到那个时候 他们会
And this time, when they come.
派出自己所有的人手 不惜一切来抓她
they're gonna come with everything they've got.
我不会丢下你的
I'm not leaving you.
你当然不会
You're not.
是我要离开你了
I'm leaving you.
去吧 唐
Go now, Dom.
无论我们愿不愿意 战争都已经开始了
A war is coming to us, whether we like it or not.
如果我们要打这场仗
If a war is coming,
就一定要在我们最熟悉的道路上迎战他们
we're gonna face them on the streets we know best.
我支持迎战 但这也太疯狂了吧
I'm all for winging it, but this is crazy, man.
我们背后有雇佣兵拿着武器要抓我们
We got mercenaries with some real heat on us.
我不是害怕或是怎么了 但是…
I mean, I ain't scared or nothing, but…
大哥 我连把枪都没有！
Man, I don't even have a gun!
枪？
Gun?
我们拥有的可是一座城市
We got a whole city.
我们拥有的优势可能比那更多 如果他们使用天眼系统
And we may have more than that. If they use God's Eye,
他们就会监视城市里的所有摄像头来寻找我们
it'll tap the cameras around town to find our location.
那就意味着我们可以植入一个病毒
Which means we could plant a virus.
然后在他们使用的时候进入系统
And then break in when they access it.
所以你说的是要黑进我的黑客设备
So you're talking about hacking my hacking device.
聪明
It's brilliant.
没错 但还是有一个问题
Yeah, but there's one problem.
信号的强弱
The signal strength.
如果他们不进入我们两英里以内的距离我们是无法黑进去的
We can't start a hack on them until they're within a two-mile range.
- 那离得太近了 - 岂止是近？
- That's really close. - Close?
这些都是职业军人
These guys are military.
如果我们之间的距离小于两英里 我们早就死了
If they're within two miles of us, we're already dead.
我不知道你们都在想什么 但我可没打算今天就死
I don't know about y'all, but I didn't really plan on dying today.
想要活着只有一个办法
Only one way to stay alive.
- 我们利用拉姆齐戏耍他们 - 什么？
- We play keep-away with Ramsey. - What?
如果我们一直在移动 他们就打不到我们
They can't hit us if we keep moving.
然后我去对付肖
And I'll take Shaw.
所以 总的来说 就是我们全副武装 然后玩烫手山芋的游戏 是吗？
So, basically, we're just gearing up for a big game of hot potato, huh?
- 哪辆车是烫手山芋？- 妹子 你才是烫手山芋
- Which car is the potato? - Girl, you're the potato.
为什么我觉得我可能再也见不到你了？
Why does it feel like I'm not gonna see you again?
我会回来取这个的
I'll come back for that.
保证吗？
Promise?
我保证
Promise.
- 布莱恩 你没事吧？- 米娅 听着
- Brian, are you okay? - Mia, listen to me.
有事要发生了
Something's about to go down.
如果我没有在24小时之内再联系你
And if you don't hear from me in 24 hours,
那你就要带着杰克继续生活了
I need you to take Jack and move on.
你听懂了吗？
You understand?
你懂我意思了吗？
You understand what I'm saying?
不 我做不到 布莱恩
No, I can't do that, Brian.
不行 我做不到
No, I can't.
我们要有第二个孩子了
We're gonna have another baby.
是个女孩
It's a little girl.
她需要她的爸爸
And she's going to need her father.
所以你要做的就是完成手头的事情
So you have to finish what you're doing.
然后回到她的身边
and you have to come home to her.
你一定要回到我们身边
You have to come home to us.
对不起 我之前没告诉你
I'm sorry I didn't tell you before.
我担心你会对家庭生活感到失落
I was scared you'd be disappointed with domestic life.
你知道吗 我这辈子做过的最棒决定就是走进那家杂货店
You know, the best decision I ever made was stepping into the store.
然后买了那第一块三明治
and buying that first sandwich.
那三明治可真是难吃
It was such a bad sandwich.
我知道 但我还是吃了好多
I know, right? But I ate a lot of them.
我爱你 米娅
I love you, Mia.
别这么说话
Don't do that.
什么？
What?
你说爱我的方式
The way you said it.
听起来像是诀别 说点别的什么
It's like goodbye. Say something else.
好吧 替我吻杰克
Okay. Kiss Jack for me.
我会的
I will.
我爱你 布莱恩
I love you, Brian.
我爱你 米娅
I love you, Mia.
最后一程
One last ride.
开启天眼系统 找到他们
Boot up God's Eye. Find them.
我发现了点东西
I'm getting something.
我发现了其中一个 是托莱多
I got a positive ID. It's Toretto.
天眼系统显示他在第七街和希尔街交界处
God's Eye is placing him at Hill and Seventh.
我们要跟着他吗？
Should we follow him?
不用 让肖对付他
No. Let Shaw take care of him.
找拉姆齐
Find Ramsey.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
我不明白为什么我们要这么一直这么开
I don't know why we gotta keep driving around like this.
我们为什么不能直接找个地方
Why can't we just pull over somewhere,
像堡垒之类的 然后就缩在里面不出来？
park, gather our thoughts in, like, a bunker somewhere?
因为这样是行不通的
Because it does not work like that.
我们要离那些坏人足够近
We gotta stick close enough to the bad guys.
好让拉姆齐黑进去
in order to get in range for Ramsey to hack them.
但是我们又要离那些人足够远 不让他们把我们当靶子打
But we gotta be mobile enough not to get shot like fish in a barrel.
你就帮帮忙 专注点开车 别把我们都害死了
So, do me a favor, focus on the mission and keep us from getting killed.
找到她了 目标锁定
Got her. Target acquired.
她坐在一辆蓝色GT-R的副驾驶上
She's riding shotgun in a blue GT-R.
各位 他们来了
Guys, they're here.
多少辆车？
How many cars?
一辆都没有
None.
这也是问题的关键
And that's kind of the problem.
好 牵着他们鼻子走
Okay, let's give them the tour.
听我口令分开走
Break on my mark.
三 二 一
Three, two, one.
走！
Go!
分开走也是没用的
Splitting up won't work.
你们躲不过天眼系统的
Can't hide from God's Eye.
他们进入有效范围了
They're in range.
拉姆齐 开始黑他们的系统
Ramsey, start the hack.
正在启动
Initiating.
好了
Now.
长官 我发觉有人正在黑进我们的系统
Sir, I think someone's trying to hack the system.
是拉姆齐
It's Ramsey.
派出捕食者无人机！
Send in the Predator!
杀了她！
Take her out!
派出捕食者
Releasing Predator.
我觉得我们好像甩掉直升机了
I think we lost the chopper.
我觉得我们面临比直升机更大的问题！
I think we got bigger problems than that!
天啊
Oh, my God.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
用老办法！
We're going old school!
小心！
Watch out!
它又绕回来了！
It's coming back around!
捕食者重新锁定他了
Predator's back on him.
- 准备导弹！- 遵命
- Ready missiles! - Roger that.
发射！
Fire!
该死！
Oh, shit!
我被盯上了！我要把人换到你那里去！
Football's hot! I need to lateral!
罗曼 你在哪？
Rom, where are you?
正全速朝你那边赶！
Running back charging in!
- 在第三街和斯布林街碰头 - 没问题！
- Meet me on Third and Spring. - You got it!
完成一半了
I'm halfway there.
拿着你的电脑！从窗户出去！
Grab your computer! Get in the window!
- 为什么？- 照做！快点！
- Why? - Do it! Now!
你得走了！就现在！
You gotta go! Right now!
发射！
Fire!
快点！
Come on!
命中了！
Hit!
他逃脱了！
He made it!
真不敢相信我们连这都做到了
I can't believe we pulled that off.
- 等等 我们的系统还在被攻击 - 什么？
- Wait, wait. We're still being hacked. - What?
天眼系统还能追踪到拉姆齐
God's Eye is still tracking Ramsey.
继续让无人机追踪她
Keep the drone in pursuit of her.
信号肯定是从某个地方传出来的
The signal has to be coming from somewhere.
重新开球 闪电进攻 被94号拦截！
Back to throw. Here comes the blitz. Number 94 sacks him!
洛杉矶晚间突发新闻
Breaking news out of Los Angeles tonight.
这只能说是一场汽车大战
In what can only be described as vehicular warfare,
警察被卷入了一场高速追逐…
police are engaged in a high-speed pursuit…
我知道了他们是利用那边那个卫星信号塔黑进来的
I got it. They're piggybacking the hack off that satellite tower right there.
炸了它！
Take it out!
托莱多
Toretto.
等等 怎么回事？我们差点就成功了
Wait. What happened? We were almost there.
他们把信号切断了！我不能继续入侵了！
They've cut the signal! I can't finish the hack!
什么意思？
What do you mean?
布莱恩 他们炸掉了信号塔！
Brian, they took out the tower!
爸爸 怎么了？
Dad, what's going on?
爸爸要去工作了
Daddy's gotta go to work.
好了 宝贝女儿
All right, baby girl.
伊莲娜马上就会到这里的
Elena's gonna be here in a little bit.
老规矩
You know our drill.
对拳三下 祝我好运
Give me three for the road.
你以为我是来街头斗殴的吗？
You thought this was gonna be a street fight?
没错 这就是街头斗殴
You're goddamn right it is.
肯定还有其它办法
There has to be another way.
等等 我看到六座信号塔
Wait. I'm seeing half a dozen.
都在第六街和州立街之间
cell towers between Sixth and State.
布莱恩 如果你能爬到其中任何一栋大楼顶上
Brian, if you can get to the top of any one of those buildings around there,
我们就能手动的重新连接上信号 然后完成任务
we can reroute the signal manually and finish the job.
马上去
I'm on it.
长官 你听到了吗？
Sir, did you hear that?
奥康纳在徒步行动 目标是中继器
O'Conner is on foot, heading for a repeater.
他要重新启动无线入侵
He's going to try to reinitiate the hack.
控制无人机盯住那个女孩
Keep the drone on the girl.
基特 奥康纳在第六街和州立街附近
Kiet, O'Conner's on foot somewhere between Sixth and State.
别让他到达转接塔
Don't let him make it there.
条子在追我们！
Them boys is on us!
该死 他们根本不知道是怎么回事！
Man, them boys ain't ready for this!
可恶！
Shit!
先是坦克 再来飞机
First the tank, then the plane.
现在换宇宙飞船了？
Now we got a spaceship?
- 别瞎说 那是无人机！- 噢 无人机？
- That's not a spaceship, that's a drone! - Oh, it's a drone?
这种情势下 你还要慢条斯理地
Now, you gonna break it down and be articulate.
跟我详细讲解是怎么回事吗？
like you already know what the hell is going on?
闭嘴 好好开车！
Shut your ass up and drive the car!
莱蒂 我们撑不住了！
Letty, the football's on fire!
请求支援！
We need help!
坚持下！我来了！
Hang on! I'm coming!
拉姆齐 准备好再次跳车！
Ramsey, get ready to go again!
- 无人机导弹锁定 - 发射！
- Drone has missile lock. - Fire!
目标摧毁
Target destroyed.
让我检查下是否还有信号 如果我可以重新连上…
Let's see if we have a connection. If I can get back in…
等等 等等！天眼还能追踪到她
Wait, wait, wait! God's Eye still has her.
怎么可能？
How can that be?
起来 快！
Get up. Come on!
上车！快！
Let's go! Let's go!
- 他们在桥下让她换车了 - 什么？
- They switched her under the bridge. - What?
赶快离开 无人机正向你飞去 速度很快
Gotta get out of here. It's on your trail and it's coming fast.
收到
Got it.
如果这辆车也被毁 谁来救我们？
So, if this car goes down, who's coming to save us?
救我们？这是最后一辆了
Save us, honey? We're it.
他们在哪？
Where are they now?
东边过六个街区 开溜中
Six blocks east, hauling ass.
该怎么走 特吉？
Where are we headed, Tej?
过了维修区就有服务电梯
There's a service elevator past the maintenance sector.
它直通中继器楼层
It'll take you directly up to the repeater.
布莱恩 动作要快！
Brian, you gotta hurry!
太慢了！
Too slow!
它绕回来了！
It's coming back!
我们进隧道 甩掉它
We'll lose them in the tunnel.
- 已瞄准 - 开火！
- Got it. - Fire!
根本甩不掉它！
I can't shake this thing!
掠夺者导弹已锁定
Predator has missile lock.
干掉它！
Take it out!
牛
No way.
等等！又怎么了？
Wait! What happened?
长官 有人摧毁了无人机
Sir, someone just double-tapped our drone.
什么？
What?
嘿 带上装甲部队了吗？
Hey, did you bring the cavalry?
女士 我即装甲
Woman, I am the cavalry.
当然是
Of course you are.
他是谁？
Who is that?
他叫霍布斯
That's Hobbs.
我到中继器面前了
I'm at the repeater.
接入电缆在底部
The access cable's in the base.
将电缆插入你的手机 拉姆齐就能连上无线了
Just plug it into your phone and Ramsey will be back online.
拉姆齐 可以了！
Ramsey, go!
布莱恩成功了 连接恢复！
Brian did it. We're back in!
我们夺回天眼了
We've got God's Eye back.
我们失去了天眼！
We lost the God's Eye!
什么？可恶！
What? Shit!
空军来了 距我们三分钟并不断接近中
Military's inbound. Three minutes and closing.
我们必须马上离开这里
We need to get the hell out of here.
特吉 罗曼 我去集合点了！
Tej, Roman, I'm on my way!
好 兄弟 集合点见
All right, homie, I'll see you there.
我看到托莱多了
I have eyes on Toretto.
开火会伤到肖
Shaw is in the way.
看来我们的友情到此结束了
Then it seems our friendship is at an end.
开火！
Do it!
两者街斗
Thing about street fights,
胜者为「街」
the street always wins.
再见 托莱多
Goodbye, Toretto.
干掉它！干掉那个混蛋！
Take him out! Take down the bastard!
这婊子…
This son of a…
不！
No!
低头！
Duck!
需要支援！我们被火力压制！
I need some help over here! We're getting nailed!
需要支援！
I need some backup!
不！不！婊子养的！
No! No! Son of a bitch!
他在逃跑！
He's getting away!
不！截住他！
No! Stop him!
看准了
Don't miss.
唐！
Dom!
加油 兄弟
Come on, buddy.
他有呼吸吗？
Is he breathing?
你来托起他的头部 好吗？
I want you to keep his head tilted up, all right?
像这样扶住
Keep it back like this.
捏住鼻子 保持头部翘起 对他进行人工呼吸 快
Pinch his nose, keep his head tilted. Breathe into him, now. Go.
好 撑住 唐
Good. Come on, Dom.
加油 唐 醒过来！
Come on, Dom. Come on!
该死的！给我醒过来！快呼吸！
God damn it! You come on! You breathe!
快 继续！呼气
Go, go! Breathe.
快 该死的 醒过来
Come on. Damn it. Let's go.
撑住 唐 快给我呼吸 快！撑住 唐！
Come on, Dom, I need you to breathe. Come on! Come on, Dom!
醒过来！快 兄弟
Come back! Come on, buddy.
- 停下吧 - 唐 撑住！撑住！
- Stop it. - Dom, come on! Come on!
让开！
Back off!
别这样！继续人工呼吸
Will you stop? Breathe into him.
- 放开他！- 你继续人工呼吸！
- Get off of him! - You breathe into him!
- 退后！- 你继续人工呼吸！
- Back off! - You breathe into him!
退后！
Back off!
拜托了
Please.
唐
Dom.
唐 亲爱的 我知道你现在很痛
Dom, baby. I know you're hurting right now.
但你要听我说 保持清醒
But I want you to listen. Stay awake.
把注意力集中在我身上
and focus on me.
我全都想起来了
I remember everything.
它们像洪水一样向我袭来
It came to me like a flood.
我记得在多米尼加共和国的那一晚
I remember that night in the Dominican Republic.
那晚我们结婚了
The night we got married.
你带着结婚戒指吗？
天啊…
Oh, my…
用这个行吗？
Will this do?
时间将永远停在这一刻
We have eternity in this moment.
你再也不会独自一人
You will never be alone again.
我发誓 你去哪 我就去哪
I vow wherever you go, I go.
你若飙车 我也飙车
You ride, I ride.
你打架 我也打架
You fight, I fight.
若你死在我面前 多米尼克·托莱多
And if you ever die on me, Dominic Toretto,
我也随你而去
I'm gonna die with you.
我爱你 莱蒂 我会永远爱你
I love you, Letty. I will always love you.
你死了 我也不会独活
If you die, I die.
我还没准备好离开这里
And I'm not ready to leave this place yet.
此刻我们依然拥有彼此
This moment is still ours.
我记起来了
I remember everything.
所有的一切我都记得
I remember it all.
是时候了
It's about time.
我们已经结婚的事 为什么不告诉我？
Why didn't you tell me we were married?
因为你不能告诉一个人 她爱你
Because you can't tell someone they love you.
太好了
Holy shit.
（中情局秘密关押处）
你确定带够人了吗 霍布斯？
You sure you brought enough backup with you, Hobbs?
他们可不是为了我
Oh, they ain't mine.
他们是为了保护你
They're here to protect you.
避免被我弄死
from me killing your ass.
这监狱关不住我 你知道的吧？
You do know none of this will keep me, right?
呵呵 等你挖通38英尺的钢筋混凝土
Well, once you dig through 38 feet of concrete and steel,
我会带着尸体袋在另一边用拳头迎接你
my fist and a body bag will be waiting for you on the other side.
我建议你现在就开始挖 小子
So I suggest you get to digging, boy.
唔呼！
Whoo-hoo!
爸爸！快来玩
Daddy! Come play.
好
Yeah.
看着他 走过去
Look at him. Look at him.
耶 小子
Yeah, buddy.
- 该尽责了 - 是的
- Duty calls. - It does.
嘿 宝贝 快来
Hey, babe, come on.
到妈妈那去 耶！
Let's get Mama. Yeah!
跑过去
Here we go.
太阳刚落下 我也好像三分熟
Because the sun is out, I'm kind of medium rare,
但我可以干得很好 我是说相当黑
but I can get, like, well done. Like, really dark.
你推我干嘛？
What you nudging me for?
闭嘴两秒钟
Close your mouth for two seconds.
看那儿 伙计
Just open your eyes, man.
美
Beautiful.
他属于那里
That's where he belongs.
家
Home.
他永远的归属
Where he's always belonged.
现在一切都变了
Things are gonna be different now.
再来一次
One more time.
不说再见就走了吗？
You aren't going to say goodbye?
永远不说再见
It's never goodbye.
嘿 不说声再见就想逃吗？
Hey. You thought you could leave without saying goodbye?
我曾说我的生活就是一个个四分之一英里加速赛
I used to say I live my life a quarter-mile at a time.
兄弟之谊 便始于此
And I think that's why we were brothers.
因为你也这么生活
Because you did, too.
- 这是你的车 - 我的？
- This is your car. - My car?
官方的
It's official.
你们全自由了
You're all free.
这才是甜蜜的家
Home sweet home.
- 近来怎样？- 多谢邀请
- What's happening, dude? - Thanks for the invite.
开车兜兜风？
Wanna go for a drive?
不论你身在何处
No matter where you are,
不管是四分之一英里之外
whether it's a quarter-mile away.
还是相隔半个世界
or halfway across the world,
生命中最重要的就是珍惜相伴在屋檐下的家人
The most important thing in life will always be the people in this room.
此处 此刻
Right here, right now.
为家人健康干杯
Salud mi familia.
干杯
Salud.
我们永远相伴左右
You'll always be with me.
兄弟之谊长存
And you'll always be my brother.
[献给保罗]